Tooltip_EN = {
    Tooltip_ArmyCrateMQ03 = "Heavy Army Supply Crate.<br>It contains unopened ammo boxes.",
    Tooltip_SupplyTicket = "Supply Request Form.<br>It can be used as currency in the bunker.",
    Tooltip_RoadControlPlan = "Road Control Plan.<br>It can be used to build a road to Westpoint.",
    Tooltip_OperationCleanSlatePlan = "Operation Clean Slate Plan.<br>It is a plan for an operation to clean up the area.",
    Tooltip_NBCEquipmentCrate = "CBRN Equipment Crate.<br>Contains radiation protective gear and decontamination supplies.",
    Tooltip_DetaineeVisitationVoiceLog = "An audio recording of a transferred officer's meeting with their attorney at a military facility.<br>The  timestamp is dated to the first day the large-scale pandemic began, and it mentions the Delta Facility, Plan B, and Louisville International Airport.",
    Tooltip_PatientFile = "A file folder containing a patient's medical history and test results from Cotman Medical.",
    Tooltip_DeltaFacilityDocument = "Documents related to the Delta Facility.<br>Includes the facility's location, entry procedures, and emergency  response guidelines.",
    Tooltip_InfectionSuppressorBox = "A box containing infection suppressants.<br>Inside are a complex dosing guide that's hard for non-professionals to    decipher, along with sterilized, sealed medication.<br>If it isn't refrigerated as soon as possible, it will spoil quickly.",
    Tooltip_LastLetterToDoctor = "A letter written through a high fever and fading consciousness, apologizing to an ex-husband.<br>It asks whoever finds    it to deliver it to Cotman Medical in Muldraugh.",
    Tooltip_RareAlcohol = "A rare liquor from a brewery the bartender used to do business with.<br>Valuable enough to boost morale in the bunker.",
    Tooltip_PrototypeWeaponBlueprint = "Blueprints for an experimental weapon known as the XM-19.<br>Detailed notes cover the firearm's design, material    specifications, and manufacturing process.",
    Tooltip_LivingSpaceFloorPlanUpper = "Floor plan for the upper level of the living quarters.<br>Use to unlock the upper level of the living quarters.",
    Tooltip_LivingSpaceFloorPlanLower = "Floor plan for the lower level of the living quarters.<br>Use to unlock the lower level of the living quarters.",
    Tooltip_OverrideCommand = "Part of a document explaining the override commands used to forcibly shut down the facility.",
    Tooltip_FitnessBooster = "An unidentified drug that boosts endurance.<br>Use to gain +1 Fitness (max 10).",
    Tooltip_StrengthBooster = "An unidentified drug that boosts physical strength.<br>Use to gain +1 Strength (max 10).",
    Tooltip_ReloadingBook = "A reloading manual written by the gunner.<br>Use to gain +1 Reloading (max 10).",
    Tooltip_AimingBook = "A marksmanship guide written by the gunner.<br>Use to gain +1 Aiming (max 10).",
    Tooltip_NimbleBook = "A booklet filled with outfit designs and tailoring tips drawn by the designer.<br>It explains how to modify everyday clothes for  easier movement.<br>Use to gain +1 Nimble (max 10).",
    Tooltip_FirstAidBook = "A first-aid handbook written by the doctor.<br>Use to gain +1 First Aid (max 10).",
    Tooltip_MassSupplyTicket = "A requisition form for a large supply payout.<br>In the bunker, it's used almost like currency.",
    Tooltip_LittleSupplyTicket = "A requisition form for a small supply payout.<br>In the bunker, it's used almost like currency.",
    Tooltip_WoundTimeReducer = "Apply to an injured body part to reduce its remaining recovery time by 50% and suppress zombie infection for a limited time.<br>If the wound is close to healing, it fully heals the injury instead.",
    Tooltip_InsulinSyringe = "An insulin syringe.<br>A relatively valuable medicine in the apocalypse.",
    Tooltip_WaterFilter = "A water filter.<br>A consumable that's hard to come by these days.",
    Tooltip_StrongNarcotics = "A powerful narcotic painkiller.<br>Too dangerous for non-professionals to use, but extremely valuable as medicine.",
    Tooltip_CommunicationDevice = "High-end communications relay equipment.<br>An expensive consumable produced through precision manufacturing.",
    Tooltip_DawnOfDeadVideo = "A low-budget horror movie on VHS.<br>It's not exactly top-quality, but for some reason it's treated as a highly rare collectible.",
}